Won't competitors
undercut me?
Ashley Christian  ·  Groundbreaker Marketing
what if
I'm not sure
about publishing
my prices because
then my
competitors are
going to know
what my prices
are
And then they're
going to undercut
me
by 50 bucks for
a pump out or
whatever it is
And the answer to
that is that your
competitors
already know what
your prices are
It's probably not
a secret
you've probably
had phone calls
like that already
that you're like
I think this
might be someone
from a competitor
just trying to
find out our
prices
that happens all
day
every day
So my response to
that is your
prices are not
actually as
secret as you
think they are